Finding aid for the Jane Sedgwick Papers
Medical Heritage Center
Jane Sedgwick Papers
1930-1999
Medical Heritage Center
Sedgwick, Jane
10.5 linear feet
This is a collection of primarily photographs and negatives that appeared in the Ohio State University College of Medicine Journal.
Spec.199817.Sedgwick
Scope and Content
The Jane Sedgwick Papers (approximately 10.5 linear feet) is a compilation of material that documents the Ohio State University College of Medicine Journal during Sedgwick’s time as Managing Editor. The collection is comprised mainly of photographs.
Statement of Arrangement
Series I: Departments (2 box) documents various medical center departments and groups. The series is arranged alphabetically. Series II: Events (2 boxes) documents various events held by the medical center. The series is arranged alphabetically. Series III: Other (2 boxes) is comprised of material of a more general nature. The series is arranged alphabetically. Series IV: People (5 boxes) documents people who work or worked in the medical center. The series is arranged alphabetically by a person's last name.
Restrictions on Access
The collection is open to the public and is available for viewing in the Medical Heritage Center. Materials do not circulate and must be used in the supervised reading room. Restrictions, including copyright, may exist and some materials may be too fragile to photocopy or digitize. The MHC charges for duplication services, which must be performed by staff.
Other Finding Aid
https://hsl.osu.edu/sites/default/files/Spec199817Sedgwick_1.pdf
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Subjects:
Ohio State University. College of Medicine
Detailed Description of The Collection
- Series I: Departments (2 boxes) documents various medical center departments and groups. The series is arranged alphabetically., 1928-1996
  - Administration, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allergy, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Omega Alpha, 1960-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Donations Information, 1972-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Office, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Anatomy, 1954-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anesthesiology, 1961-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bennett Research Society, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Chairs-Journal Full Page-Summer 1986, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chairs, Professorships (College of Medicine), 1971-1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Child Psychiatry, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Clinical Divisions Oct 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Clinical Divisions Organization, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Clinical Pathology Labs, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Clinical Research Center, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - College of Medicine Display, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Computerization in Hospitals, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Cooperative Human Tissue Network (Clausen), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Creative Living, 1970-1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CT Scanner, Fall 1984 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Davis Center-OSU Arthritis and Aging, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Day Care/Bone Marrow, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dayton Veterans Administration Hospital, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Department of Medicine, 1954-1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Diabetes/Atherosclerosis Center, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Endowment Annual Dinner (5), 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Epilepsy, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Family Primary Care Curriculum, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Visitors, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Funds Established for Medicine -COM, 1977-1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Gait Laboratory Analysis, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Geriatrics, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Graduate Programs, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Headache Clinic-Neurology, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Hearing-Impaired Patients, 1977-1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hippocrates Plaza, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hippocratic Oath, No Date (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - History Book 25 year, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Honorary Degrees, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Hospitals Board, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Hospitals Health Services Admin, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Hospital Health Services Division, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - House Officers and Wives Club, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Internship Match (1987, 1988) and Residency Listing (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Intro-operative Radiation Therapy (IORT), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Labs for Knowledge-Based Medical Systems, Dr. Jack Smith, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Landacre Society, 1956-1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Magnetic Resonance Imaging and Facility (MRI)-1985, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Mammography-Olsen, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Med I Program, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Medical Alumni Society-OSU1934-1990, Book Draft (Published), 1991 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Medical Alumni Society-OSU 1934-1990, Book Preparation, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Medical Education/Students, 1963-1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Medical History Group, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Medical Humanities Program, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Medical Microbiology, 1965-1975 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Medical Microbiology Graduate Program, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Medical Students-Assorted Stories, 1976-1988 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Medical Student Brochure, 1954-1961 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Medical Student Photos (1 of 3), 1964-1986 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Medical Student Photos (2 of 3), 1967-1990 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Medical Student Photos (3 of 3), 1967-1990 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Medical Student Smart Program, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Minority Recruiting-Affirmative Action, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Neurology Department, 1964-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Nisonger Center, 1975-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Nisonger Toy Library, No Date (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Nite Out, 1954-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Otolaryngology, 1968-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Nite Out 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Obstetrics/Gynecology, 1960-1985 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Ohio Eminent Scholars Program, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Ophthalmology, 1965-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Order of Hippocrates-Alumni Club, 1957-1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Organ Transplantations, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Parents Weekend, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Pathology, 1954-1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Pediatrics, 1961-1987 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Pediatric Surgery, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Pharmacology, 1974-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Pharmacology-Graduate Program, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Photos, 1930's-1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Photos, 1928-1981 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Photos-House Staff (1 of 2), 1966-1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Photos-House Staff (2 of 2), 1965-1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Physical Therapy, 1954-1975 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Physiology, 1954-1986 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Physiological Chemistry, 1955-1975 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Physiological Chemistry, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Physiology-Graduate Program, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Preceptor Program, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Preventative Medicine, 1954-1971 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Psychiatry, 1953-1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Pulmonary Diseases, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Radioisotopes, 1953-1962 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Radiology, 1954-1984 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Radiation Therapy Facility, 1948-1979 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Rehab Center-Kenny Road (1984) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - SAMA/SNMA, 1961-1988 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - SAMP, 1969-1983 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Sky Med, 1987-1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Sleep Lab-Upham Hall, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Spina Bifida Clinic-Myelomeningocele, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Sports Medicine, 1971-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Student Council, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Support Groups for Medical Students, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Surgery, 1954-1984 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Surgery Intensive Care Unit, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Testimonial Dinner 1974 Dr. Meiling and Dr. Zollinger (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - University Hospitals-Transplantations, 1984-1996 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - VA Clinic, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - VA Outpatient, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Wheelchair-Miss America Pageants, 1974-1977 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Wheelchair Races-1972 and Queen-1974, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Women in Basic Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Women in Medicine-Spring '87, 1971-1987 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Women in Science-OSU Alumnae, 1968-1981 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Series II: Events (2 boxes) documents various events held by the medical center. The series is arranged alphabetically., 1950-1990
  - AAMC, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - AMSA Stethoscope Heart-to-Heart, Winter 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Picnic for Graduating Senior Summer, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Reunion April 10, 1965-April 16, 1966 (College of Medicine), 1961-1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Reunion-1967 Pix and Programs-April 22 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Reunion-April 20, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Reunion-1969 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alumni Reunion-April 17-18, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Alumni Reunion-May 7, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 15-16, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 15, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 21, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Reunion-1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 10-11, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 16-17, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 29-30, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 7-8, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 12-13, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 11-12, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 10-11, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 9-10, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 7-8, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 13-14, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 19-20, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Alumni Reunion-September 11-12, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Anatomy Cadaver Memorial Service, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Anatomy Graduate Program, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Archives, 1973-1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Atrium-Rhodes Hall, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - "Black Bag" (Computer) Program, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Bone Marrow-Tutschka, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bozler Plaque Dedication, Winter 1990 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Burn Unit, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - CCMI-For Publication, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - CCME ind. OMEN, 1964-1987 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Convocation 1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Convocation July 1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Convocation July 1972 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Convocation July 1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Convocation July 1974 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Convocation July 1977 E 7 '77 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Convocation E 7 '78 July 1978 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Convocation 1978? (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Convocation July 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Convocation June 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Convocation September 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Convocation June 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Convocation September 1981 (and some July Pix of ISP Reception) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Convocation September 1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Convocation September 11, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Convocation September 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Convocation September 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Convocation September 1986 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Convocation September 1988 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Convocation and Orientation 1955-1956 and 1960's, 1950's and 1960's (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Convocation and Orientation E 7 '75 July, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Convocation and Orientation July 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Convocation and Orientation Pix-Stories, 1964-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Convocation, No Date (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Convocation-Reception following, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1972 (Senior Dinner Pictures) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1973 (the last MED) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 12, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1979 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 8, 1979? (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 1982 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Doctoral Convocation-June 9, 1983 (Graduation June 10, 1983) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Doctoral Convocation (and Graduation)-June 7, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Doctoral Convocation June 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Doctoral Convocation June 1986 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Doctoral Convocation June 1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Doctoral Convocation July 9, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Fall Convocation 1987 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Grads/Alumni Luncheon 1987 Graduation-Stadium 1987 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Honors Night Programs June 1967-August 9, 1970, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Intern Match-March 13, 1985 and Residency Listing (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Internship List Preparation Spring Issues (matching picture), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Internship Match 1979 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Internship Matching 1975-1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Medical Alumni Society Ex Comm. Meeting, October 30, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Medical Student Art Exhibit, February 1990 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Senior Class Parties May 1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Senior Class Party 1974 (May, June) (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Senior Class Party 1975 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Senior Dinner-Dance (June 1971) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Senior Dinner Dance Class of 1976 (and Stadium Graduation) (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Series III: Other (2 boxes) is comprised of material of a more general nature. The series is arranged alphabetically., 1934-1990
  - 1934 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1935 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1936 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 1937 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - 1938 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - 1939 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1940-1946 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - 1947 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - 1948 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 1951 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 1989 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Advertising, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Area Associate Form Letters (By Quarters) (1 of 2), 1966-1987 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Area Associate Form Letters (By Quarters) (2 of 2), 1953-1968 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Beaver Press, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Bids for Printing, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Bids Info for Journal, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Bids Info for Journal, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Central Printing, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - College of Medicine Journal (21 photos), Spring 1978 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Capsule Cases, 1953-1963 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Children's Hospital, 1954-1966 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Clippings - Medical - Nat'l Media, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - C.O.M. Progress Fund, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - CV's - Biography Forms - Students, 1977-1988 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - CV's - House Officers, 1982-1988 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - DeBakey, Michael E., 1960-1967 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Editorials, 1954-1961 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Feature Stories, 1953-1956 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - HCJ Research Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Home Bindery, 1978-1982 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Journal Financial, 1961-1979 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Journal (Scheduling-Printing/Content Info.) Jane Sedgwick 4225672, No Date (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Medical Center Profile-Nursing Students, 1976-1988 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Medical Center Profile-Nursing Students....Cont, 1967-1988 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Medical Microwave, 1973-1976 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Medical Students, 1954-1961 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Negs. 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Negs. Proofs-Fall 1979 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Negs. & Proof of Sheets - Spring '80, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Negs. Proof Sheets - Summer '80 Issue, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Negs. - Fall 1980 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Negs. Proof Sheets - Winter 1980 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Negs. - Spring 1981 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Negs. - Summer 1981 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Negs. Fall 1981 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Negs. - Winter 1981 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Negs. - Spring Issue 1982 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Negatives - Summer 1982 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Negatives - Fall '82, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Negs. - Winter Issue 1982 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Negatives - Spring '83, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Negatives - Summer '83, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Fall 1983 - Negs. (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Negatives - Winter '83, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - OSU College of Med. Journal - Jane, 1969-1989 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - OSU College of Med. Journal - Jane, 1979-1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - OSU Positions - P>R. etc., 1970-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Photographs-Misc., Groups, Unidentified Nursing Profiles, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Pony-x-Press Typesetting, 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Practice Plan, 1977-1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Printing Bid Info, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Public Relations Letters, 1959-1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Retired/Deceased, 1970-1987 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Robin Enterprises, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Scheduling - Summer 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Television, 1956-1961 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Thanks and General Letters, 1959-1962 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Trebiekowski & John Kewph, M.D, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - TV Circuit in Hospital, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Unclassified Photos, 1955-1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Series IV: People (5 boxes) documents people who work or worked in the medical center. The series is arranged alphabetically by a person's last name., 1943-1999
  - Ackerman, Adolph, 1976-1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Ainsworth, Marion & Louise, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Alben, James O., 1962-1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Alexander, Michael, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Hugh, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Altman, Michael, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Altschuld, Ruth, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ambuel, Philip, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Clark -RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Andresen, Brian D., 1978-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Andrews, Neil, 1961-1966 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Anthony, Joseph R., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Armstrong, Milton, No Date (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Arnold, Lawrence Eugene, 1973-1985 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Assor, Dieter, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Atwell, Robert J., 1966-1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Ayers, Leona, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Azimi Parvin, 1970-1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Baba, N, No Date (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Baker, Bruce -RESTRICTED, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Balcerzak, Stanley, 1967-1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Barth, Rolf -RESTRICTED, 1979-1987 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Batley, Frank, 1968-1983 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Beman, Floyd M., 1958-1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Benes, Susan, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Bianchine, Joseph R. & Josette, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Biersdorf, William, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Binkley, William, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bitonte, Joseph L., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Bobulski, Rosalind, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Boles, Thomas E. Jr., 1954-1992 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Bonta, Joseph A., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Boudoulas, Olga, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Boulant, Jack, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Bouroncle, Bertha A., 1953-1999 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Bova, James -RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Bowen, Juan, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Bowman, Bernard, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Boyers, Pam -RESTRICTED, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Bozler, Emil, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Braddom, Randall L., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Brierley, Gerald P. -RESTRICTED, 1966-1983 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Bromberg, Philip, 1968-1974 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Brown, John B., 1952-1970 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Browning, Robert H., 1953-1962 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Bull, David, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Bullock, Thomas, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Bunn, Paul David, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Burghes, Arthur, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Burke, John, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Bush, Charles, 1976-1991 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Caldwell, James, 1970-1986 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Camisa, Charles, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Campbell, Donald, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Cataland, Sam -RESTRICTED, 1970-1988 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Cerilli, G. James, 1967-1974 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Chakeres, Donald W. -RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Chen, Moon S., 1992 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Chidley, John, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Chiles, John, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Chirikos, Thomas, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Chiu, Ing Ming, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Christofordis, A. John -RESTRICTED, 1982-1990 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Clairmont, Albert, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Clark, Robert, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Clausen, Kathryn -RESTRICTED, 1974-1993 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Clayworthy, H. William Jr., 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Cleverly, William, 1981-1987 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Coddington, R. Dean, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Cody, Robert, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Cooke, Helen -RESTRICTED, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Copeland, Larry, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Copeland, William Jr., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Copeland, William Sr., 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Cordero, Leandro, 1971-1984 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Cornhill, Fred, 1982-1988 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Cornwell, David, 1967-1985 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Corrigan, John D., 1993 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Covert, Michael H., 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Craig, Elson, 1972-1990 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Cramblett, Henry G., 1964-1992 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Cramp, Donald, 1980-1984 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Cunningham, Jerome, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Curry, John, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Curtiss, Paul, 1965-1978 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - D'Ambrosio, Stephen, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Davidorf, Fred, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - DeLeo, Bernard, 1969-1974 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Delphia, John Maurice, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - DePhilip, Robert, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - DeVor, Arthur, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Doan, Charles, 1946-1961 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Doan, Charles, No Date (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Donnerberg, Roy L., 1955-1987 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Downs, John B. -RESTRICTED, No Date (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Drake, Miles -RESTRICTED, 1982-1985 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Duran, Robert, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Earl, William C., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Eaton, Antoinette -RESTRICTED, 1981-1990 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Edwards, Linden F., 1954-1970 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Egilitis, John A. & Irma, 1967-1986 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Ehlers, Gunther, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Ellison, Edwin H., 1943-1963 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Enarson, Harold, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Enrile, Benedicta G., 1982-1987 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Eptropoulis, Alice, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Ertel, Paul and Inta, 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Essig, Garth, 1973-1988 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Evans, Helen, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Evans, Lloyd R., 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 110)